A car that runs on water instead of
gasoline, can it be true? Well, inventor
Stanley Meyer made an announcement today
in Colorado Springs. He says he's come
up with a device that will hook up to
any engine and allow it to run on good
old H2O. News 13's Kurt Goff tonight on
the possible impact of the water fuel
cell.
Stanley Meyer says the answer to
dependence on foreign oil lies all
around us.
In seawater, tap water, and rain water.
Any kind of H2O, he says, can power just
about every type of engine.
How? With the water fuel cell. It fits
in the palm of his hand, but it could
revolutionize the world.
You're talking about a pollution-free,
totally new source of energy. The
voltage disassociation of water.
The fuel cell converts water into a gas,
hydrogen oxygen, which is released in
the form of thermo explosive energy.
So, the water fuel injector simply
replaces the spark plug. We hook it to a
hydrogen computer system which regulates
and meters the flow going into the
injector. It processes the water in such
a way to release its thermal explosive
energy.
The man who invented an engine that can
run on water says he's been offered a
billion dollars in cash by oil-producing
countries to sell his patent. So far, he
hasn't sold. Environmental specialist
Jan Porter talked to the inventor who
thinks that the US auto industry could
produce cars that run on water now if
they wanted to.
Our industrial base of the world is
based on the utilization of
Stanley Meyer has a car that runs on
water, and that's drawing crowds at this
year's extraordinary science conference
in Colorado Springs. Myers has developed
what is called the water fuel cell
injector. The injector breaks down the
water molecule into hydrogen and oxygen,
and the hydrogen is what powers the car.
Basically, all we do is replace uh
the spark plug and replace it with the
water fuel cell injectors you see right
here. We simply feed ordinary
non-processed water or processed water
in here and as the water goes into the
injector
uh it hits a very high pulse voltage
frequency which instantly converts it
into thermal explosive energy and as a
result we can run this car down the road
on water.
Meyer's invention was introduced in
Britain earlier this month and now the
Brits have followed him here.
that we recently took a scientific
delegation
to witness Stan's work, to really
evaluate it and came back saying
this is one of the most important
inventions of the century.